by H.
Here we go, upgami, this time with Riko Yamagishi of Tsubaki Factory and Ori Yagishi of Tsubaki Factory.
This is a program that takes you behind the scenes of the production of various artists belonging to the Upfront Group.
We will show you the process of recording and rehearsal.
I, Yamagishi, have been thinking that there are many Tsubaki factory pes this summer.
We're going to hold a show called "Burning Hot" at Kawaguchi Costella Theater on August 24th, and I went last year.
This year, too, we will have a strategy meeting, and I'm sure it will be a lot of fun because it will be created by everyone.
I hope that many of you will come to this event.
We will be performing at Uppity Presents Shine Fest 2023 and Tokyo Idol Festival 2023.
I'm sure these events will be fun as well, so please come and enjoy them.
There are going to be a lot of festivals and outdoor performances in the summer, so I've been thinking that I need to get in shape, especially since it's been so hot lately.
I recently took ballet lessons and learned a new way to stretch my legs.
The stretching technique is to make the arch of the sole of the foot beautiful.
To make the arches of the soles of the feet more beautiful.
Like this? That's right.
That's great! And strengthen the muscles.
Oh, you're going to fish!
I'll fish!
I myself have a tendency to walk in a way that squashes my arches, and I don't use my back muscles, the hamstrings.
I have pointed out that I am not using my back muscles, the hamstrings, in the way I walk.
If I fix that, my legs will become thinner and my side legs will be healed.
I see...
That's what I'm trying to achieve!
Then, I should try it, too.
Yes, I think you should try it.
I'll give it a try.
Let's start with this time's up-kami, here.
Juice-Juice Funky Flashin
Making of music video shooting
Released on July 12!
Juice-Juice's latest singleFrom Juice-Juice's latest single
Watch the music video shooting of Funky Flash Inn!
BGM.
Yes, we have started shooting the music video for FUNKY FLASH...
Well, it was very summery and the weather was very fine today.
The weather is really fine today.
I wrote "I hope it will be fine" and it was fine.
I wrote that I hoped it would be sunny, and I'm glad it turned out fine.
I haven't seen everyone's costumes yet.
I'm really interested in the atmosphere of the costumes.
Is the lip scene cheerful?
I was wondering if it would be cheerful. I was wondering...
I thought it would be more mature.
I thought the range of my expression would expand.
I think the range of expression will expand with this shoot.
Thank you for your patience.
Now, please turn the recording around.
Please do.
BGM
Invite someone to come and listen.
Let's spend the night that's about to begin.
Stay alone in your room
The loneliness won't go away
Get into the rhythm
Clap your hands
I'm humming along
Her love song
Step on the steps
I know I can dance
Oh, Let's Play Wonderful Music
Let's dance Disco till morningLet's dance Disco till morning
Let's make funky night
If you hear it once
I'll miss you
You'll forget how honest you are
This time, we're shooting a summery music video in a place that's a bit like a house studio.
We're shooting a summery music video in a house studio with a swimming pool and stuff.
Juice Juice. It's pretty rare for us to release a single in the summer.
I think it's rare to release a single in the summer.
I hope you can enjoy Juice Juice in the summer with all the excitement of summer.
I'll do my best to shoot the video with lots of smiles on my face.
Invite someone to come and listen to the song.
Let's spend the night together.
I'll dream alone
Invite someone to come and listen
Alone in my room, the loneliness won't go away
I'm clapping my hands to the rhythm
I'm humming her love song
Step on the steps and you'll be dancing
Oh, let's play wonderful music
Let's dance till morning
Let's make funky night
Once you've heard it, you'll forget how lonely it is
It's hot and it's slanted
Yes! It's slanting
The terrain is at an angle
And the angle you have to take the picture is also slanted.
It's very difficult to be parallel to everything!
And it's hot!
You should be able to dance with her LOVE SONG steps.
Play nice MusicPlay Lovely Music
Let's Dance Disco till Morning
Let's Make Funky Night
Oh Let's Play Great Music
Let's Dance Disco till Morning
Let's Make Funky Night
Oh Let's Play
Let's Make Funky Night Oh Let's Play
Disco till Morning
BGM
See You Tomorrow
See you tomorrow
What if... what if... what if it's okay?
Are you sure?
You don't get a freebie.
It's beautiful.
Sweet.
Sweet!
So sweet!
Let's Dance Morning Comes So Let's Make Funky Night Always
Play!
Dance, Dance, Dance, Disco till morning
Let's make Funky night
Thank you for your hard work!
Well, we just finished shooting the music video for FUNKY FLASHIN.
A little stylish like this?
How does it look like?
We usually do songs with a more mature look, but I think we can enjoy a different kind of mature look.
I think you can enjoy a different kind of mature look.
I think you can probably tell just from this feeling.
We were really blessed with the weather and the location.We were really blessed with great weather, including the location.
It was a really fun music video shoot.
We also had a lot of group shots, where we split up into groups of two or three people, so I don't really have an idea of how it will turn out.
We had no idea how it was going to turn out, so we are looking forward to seeing the music video with you all!
We are looking forward to seeing the music video with you all!
I thought it had a very mature atmosphere, just like JuiceJuice, just by the fact that it was at a swimming pool at night.
JuiceJuice's songs often have this kind of vibe to them.
I love those kinds of songs, so I really want to see more songs like this in the future.
It's the same when you watch the music videos and listen to the songs.
I think it's great that you can enjoy both of them.
This is the making of Juice-Juice Funky Flashing music video.
Even You Can't Take It Away
TUES-TUES PRIDE BRIGHT NOW ON SALE
I love you for trying your best.
Next, here we go!
Angelem Dousoukousei Vocal Recording
From Angulum's latest single, "Dousou Sei".
Here's a look at Ayano Kana's vocal recording.
You look tired. You look tired.
She looks tired, too, and I'm sure everyone looks better than me
I don't show it when I play
I don't show it
How's it going? How's it going?
How's that?
I'm sure everyone looks better than me. Even that girl.
I don't show it when we play.
Like that girl, I bet no one else looks better than me.
If I trusted you, you'd betray me.
I've been so scared of betrayal.
She's so pure and kind
If I trust you... If I trust you...If you believe, if you believe
If I believe, if I believe.
Betrayal. Betrayal.
If you believe, betrayal.
If I believe, I'll be betrayed
I've been so frightened.
You are genuinely kind.
I sang the song paying attention to the ending of the words and the way the words end.
The rhythm of the song was more clickety-clack than usual, so I worked hard on that,
I did my best on that.
I know that.
I know it.
Yes, I know.
I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you.
The last part of the chorus has a high and very long "aa" sound, so I was asked to sing the last line of the chorus as if I was singing it enthusiastically, so I sang it enthusiastically.
So I sang the last line with a lot of enthusiasm.
I know you were happy.
As a whole, it was the first time I sang a Tsunku III song since Sunday, the day I got up at all in 2019,
It had been a while since I sang this cheerful song,
I felt like I was singing with a different voice from the one I usually sing with Angstrom, in terms of the way I did my voice and the way I sang.
The way of rhythm and the way of ending words were something I was not used to since I hadn't recorded Tsunku III's songs in a very long time.
Thank you very much.
I have never recorded Tsunku's songs, so I don't have much experience.
I have never recorded Tsunku's songs, so I don't have much experience with it, so I don't know what to expect, but I thought the way he cuts the rhythm and the way he sings the words seems very difficult.
I thought that if I ever sing again, I would pay attention to the rhythm and try my best.
In terms of Tsubaki Factory's music, Zastri is a song written and composed by Tzunku.
I remember that I had a hard time with the rhythm when we recorded Just Try, but I learned a lot from it.
But I learned a lot from it, and I will continue to sing his songs with great care.
That's all for now, here's a glimpse at the vocal recording session of Ayano Kawamura, an alumna of Angulum.
Don't worry, I'll manage somehow.
This is up-cam by Shiori Yagi, a.k.a. Shiri Yamaki of Tsubaki Factory.Upokami is brought to you by Shiori Yagi, aka Shiri Yamaki of Tsubaki Factory.
Here is the continuation.
Tsubaki Factory's song, Seventh Blossom Continues, instrumental recording.
Here is the guitar recording of Tsubaki Factory's song "Seventh Blossom".
At first, I'm going to play once until the end of the intro.
Okay, I understand.
Is it OK if I record it?
Yes, that's fine.
That's fine.
Thank you very much.
I'm sorry, I just need the last two bars one more time.
Can you do a crescendo here?
Yes!
As much as you can get away with.
It's possible to make it too loud, right?
A little too much, and you'll get it back about the same.
Start with the weakest part.
♪ ♪
Yes, we're up.
Thank you.
I think I'll do the interlude with the momentum of the chorus.
I think we'll do the interlude at the same volume as the chorus.
I'm sure you'll want to go there.
I'm sure there's a weak point.
Let's take it when it comes.
Let's start with the chorus.
♪♪
Don't put in the last 16 minutes of the third step of C.
And instead of that, the end of the second measure of the fourth step
with this. Yes, that's what I want to do.
And I want this crescendo at E.And I want this crescendo at E.
Yes, it's soooooo good.
Yes, please.
How's it phrasing-wise?
Yes, it's nice.
Is it okay?
Yes, it's fine.
So I guess we'll just leave it at that.
Okay, let's continue.
Sunday rain
I want to go home now.
Just a little more, just a little more, just a little more.
Just a little more, just a little more.
Just a little more, just a little more
Just a little bit more
Just a little more...
I'm turning it if it's fantastically okay.
If it's fantastically okay, I'm turning it.
Can I just do the first four bars?
Yes, of course.
I'll take it then.
So I guess that means you've got this part for the electric guitar.
Yes, the right part is finished.
The electric tone was introduced in the previous video,
The electric tone was introduced in the previous video,The electric tone was introduced in the previous video,
The tone of the electric guitar was introduced in the previous video,
What about pick scratching? I'll take one.
I'll ask him to make one with a little more gun distortion.
This one?
Perfect.
I'll leave the long one.
It's not a joke.
Yes, I got it.
I guess that's all then.
Yes, that's all.Yes.
Yes, you are finished. Thank you very much.
My name is Kohei Uchida, guitarist.
Especially for the acoustic guitarist, there are some arpeggios in the A melody where the song starts that go apart,
I think the key point is to make the arpeggio phrases overlap with the melody of the song in a good way.
I played two electric guitars in this song, and the first and second guitars have slightly different tones, and I tried to create a thicker sound.
From the beginning to the end of a song, there are quite a few changes in volume and range,
I think we were able to create a good tone in the intro and a loud volume in the chorus.
This song was the first song on the spring tour, as a continuation of "Seventh Blossom.
The moment the intro started, I loved it so much that I felt like the curtain was about to open.
And the lyrics of this song really made me swoon,
I think that the first line is a sweet and sour song for high school students, and the second line is a little bit like, "What have you been up to lately?
I heard you went home from work..." The lyrics are like, "I heard you went home from work," and I guess he went down a different path.
I can feel that he still loves the girl and the boy, and all the lyrics are very touching.
The performance of this song has graceful movements and a bit of jazz, so I think it is a spring-like song that fits the atmosphere of the song,
I really like the sound of acoustic guitar,
I really like the sound of acoustic guitar, so I would like to sing with just an acoustic guitar someday.
That's a great new idea.
Thank you very much.
That was the guitar recording, a continuation of Tsubaki Factory's Shichibunsaki.
Jill Power It's mediocre, but it's a golden riff.
JACHA NO MA NEW Single
Chikinare
January 26th release
Thanks for watching.
It's time to say good-bye to the Upcami series of songs by Riko Yamagishi and Shiori Yagi. We've seen a lot of different videos this time, but I, Yagi, was left with a strong impression of the guitar playing in the recording of "Seventh Bloom".
I was really impressed by the recording video of the guitar performance of "Seventh Blossom".
I don't know if it's the left hand or the right hand, but it sounds like a different rhythm.
I don't know if it's a bit strange to compare it to a recorder, but it's like tonguing.
I don't know much about guitar technique, so I thought it was very strange and wonderful.
I see... I, Amagishi, was watching the making of JuiceJuice's music video.I see. I, Amagishi, was very impressed by the making of JuiceJuice's music video.
I was really impressed by the making of JuiceJuice's music video, and I think it's wonderful to have songs that are very summery and give a sense of the season.
I think it's very summery and it's very nice to have songs that make you feel the season, like Tsubaki Factory's "I just wanted to float tonight.
Upokami is a program that goes behind the scenes of the production of the various artists who belong to the Upfront Group.
Please subscribe to our channel and we'll introduce you to the parts you don't normally get to see.
This time upcami's partners are Rika Yamagishi from Tsubaki Factory and Ori Yagishi from Tsubaki Factory.
Good bye!
Next time on Upokami: Ochanoma, a little emotional instability, the making of the summer music video shoot.
And we'll be showing you the recording of Angsty Beast of Love.
Love you, shining us
Burning Encounter
Burning Hot Soothing